ninjacat.io 2018-10-20

# NinjaCat | privacy policy

### What Types of User Information Does NinjaCat Obtain?

### Visitors to the NinjaCat Website

If you are a visitor to the NinjaCat website or a NinjaCat client (“Client”) who registers or signs into the NinjaCat website (including for purposes of obtaining a free trial of NinjaCat’ services), we may obtain the following types of information from you or concerning your computer or device (“NinjaCat Client Information”), which may include information that can itself be used to identify and/or contact you (“Personally Identifiable Information”)

  * Name

  * Email Address

  * Phone Number

  * Website Name and URL

  * Credit Card Number

  * Billing Address

  * Visitor Site Preferences

NinjaCat may also receive certain information that may be provided by your browser or mobile device, including:

  * Browser Information

  * Operating System Information

  * Mobile Device Information (e.g., device identifier, mobile operating system, etc.)

  * IP Address

  * Pages Accessed

  * Time of Visit

  * Time of Last Visit

  * Referring Site, Application, or Service, including the relevant Search Queries that led you to NinjaCat’ Website

### Visitors to the NinjaCat Blog

If you wish to access certain functions within the NinjaCat Blog, such as posting comments or registering for webinars, we may ask you to provide information, including:

  * Name

  * Email Address

  * Your Website

### Visitors to NinjaCat’ Clients’ Websites

Our Clients may use customized and proprietary NinjaCat’ code, software and/or services (“Service”) to obtain information regarding the activities that users engage in while visiting their web pages (“Client’s User Data”). When a user visits a website that uses NinjaCat’ Service, NinjaCat code contained on the website contacts NinjaCat’ servers and enables NinjaCat to collect Client’s User Data. Some Clients may also use their own code to obtain Client’s User Data and then send such information to NinjaCat’ servers.

Client’s User Data is stored on NinjaCat’ web servers and databases for use in performing analysis and producing reports for the NinjaCat Client only. 

In addition, NinjaCat may collect certain information about a Client’s Visitor’s computer that may be provided by the Visitor’s browser. This includes browser information, operating system information, mobile device information, IP address, time of visit, and the referring site, application, or service. Such information is collected even though not determined not determined by the Client. 

Because Clients have the sole discretion to determine what Information NinjaCat collects about or from the Clients’ users, this Privacy Policy does not apply to any Client’s User Data, including Personally Identifiable Information, that NinjaCat may collect, obtain, or access in connection with operating the NinjaCat Service.

## How Do We Use This Information?

### Visitors to NinjaCat’ Clients’ Websites

We use the NinjaCat Client Information, including Personally Identifiable Information, to register your account, fulfill your requests, understand how you are engaging with NinjaCat, communicate with you, determine if you are satisfied with the Service, process billing for NinjaCat Services, and personalize your experience on the NinjaCat website and with the NinjaCat Service. 

We may also use NinjaCat User Information to facilitate the delivery of content or advertisements that we believe may be of interest to you, or to communicate with you about new or existing products and services or special offers. For more information on opting out of these communications, please see the section on “User Privacy Controls” below.

### Visitors to NinjaCat’ Clients’ Websites

Except as described in the “Disclosure of Information to Third Parties” section below, NinjaCat never sells or shares any Client’s User Data with individuals or companies other than the specific Client whose website transmitted the Client’s User Data to NinjaCat.

### Our Client’s Use of NinjaCat

NinjaCat contractually requires its Clients to abide by all applicable laws, rules and regulations, including laws relating to privacy and data collection. NinjaCat also contractually requires its Clients to obtain any necessary consents from visitors to its website(s) for the Client’s use of NinjaCat’ services, and to post an online privacy policy that provides each visitor with clear notice of its practices regarding data collection, use, and disclosure (including the Client’s use of NinjaCat), along with a link to the NinjaCat Privacy Policy and to the NinjaCat Service Opt-Out (discussed below).NinjaCat has no control over its Clients’ activities or the disclosures made by its Clients in their privacy policies or on their websites, however, and it cannot be held responsible for any Client’s failure to make these disclosures on its website or for any Client’s use or collection of Client’s User Data that is not permitted under this Privacy Policy or otherwise. For more details on the terms that apply to our Clients’ use of the NinjaCat Service, please see Section 4 (“Privacy”) in the NinjaCat Terms of Use.

### NinjaCat’ Use of Cookies and Web Beacons

### Cookies

NinjaCat uses cookies (small text files that NinjaCat stores locally on your computer) on our Client’s websites for one or more of the following purposes: to help identify unique visitors and/or devices; assess usage patterns and perform traffic analysis; identify visitor preferences; conduct A/B testing; diagnose problems with our servers, and otherwise administer the NinjaCat Service. NinjaCat does not use methods such as browser cache, Flash cookies, or eTags, for acquiring or storing information about end users web browsing activity on Client websites or otherwise. 

Depending on how our Clients use NinjaCat’ Services, information contained in NinjaCat cookies placed on the computers of end users may be linked to Personally Identifiable Information in NinjaCat’ database. This allows our Clients to use the NinjaCat Service to better analyze and measure their users’ interactions with their website and to organize activities by the same user on their website across time. 

If you do not wish to have NinjaCat place and use cookies on your computer, you should set your browser preferences to refuse all cookies before accessing NinjaCat or other websites that may use NinjaCat. NinjaCat is not responsible for any failure by you or your browser to accurately implement or communicate your browser preferences or settings. In addition, please be aware that even if you configure your browser settings to reject all cookies, your activity on NinjaCat client websites will still be recorded by our Service, unless you opt out of our Service as set forth below. However, your rejection of all cookies will prevent NinjaCat from determining whether or not someone using your computer has previously visited the website, i.e., whether or not the visitor is a “unique” visitor. 

Please note that if you set your browser to reject cookies, some features of the websites you visit may be unavailable. For more information on how to reject cookies, see your browser's instructions on changing your cookie settings. Additionally, please note that rejecting cookies may also prevent you from opting out of our Service because that involves placing an opt-out cookie in your browser. 

If you do not elect to set your browser preferences to refuse cookies, you consent to have cookies, including cookies used by NinjaCat, placed on your computer when you visit our Client’s websites.

### Web Beacons

NinjaCat may also collect certain information using Web Beacons. Web Beacons are electronic images that may be used on NinjaCat’ Website, in NinjaCat’ Service, or in our email communications. They are used, for example, to count website visits or to tell if an email has been opened and acted upon.

## Disclosure of Information to Third Parties

### Service Providers

Information, including NinjaCat Client Information, Client’s User Data, and any Personally Identifiable Information contained therein, may be shared with certain third-party companies and individuals that help facilitate technical and administrative aspects of the NinjaCat Service (e.g., credit card processing), or perform functions related to the administration of NinjaCat (e.g. hosting services). These third parties perform tasks on our behalf and are contractually obligated not to disclose or use NinjaCat User Information or Client’s User Data for any other purpose, and to employ adequate security measures to prevent unauthorized access to such data. However, NinjaCat is not responsible in the event that Personally Identifiable Information is disclosed at a result of a breach or security lapse by any such third party.

### NinjaCat Partners

If you are a NinjaCat Client that signed up through our Partners Program, your NinjaCat Client Information may be shared with the Partner Program member that signed you up for NinjaCat’ Service. These Partner Program members may use that information to help you setup, adjust, manage, and cancel your account with NinjaCat.

### Law Enforcement and Legal Process

NinjaCat also reserves the right to disclose any NinjaCat Client Information or Client User Information (including Personally Identifiable Information) to: (i) comply with any law, regulation, or legal request; (ii) enforce, apply, or investigate breaches of the Terms of Use or other agreements; (iii) respond to client requests; or (iv) protect the rights, property, user experience, or safety of NinjaCat, our employees, our users, or others.

### Change of Control

If NinjaCat, or substantially all of its assets, is acquired by another company or successor entity, NinjaCat Client Information and/or Client’s User Data will be one of the assets transferred or acquired by the purchaser or successor. You acknowledge that such transfers may occur, and that any purchaser of or successor to NinjaCat or its assets may continue to collect, use and disclose your information acquired prior to such transfer or acquisition as set forth in this policy.

## User Privacy Controls

### Clients and Visitors to the NinjaCat Website

NinjaCat offers several ways for you to update or delete Personally Identifying Information that is obtained and stored by NinjaCat, or to change your NinjaCat communication preferences:

  * You may unsubscribe to any of our e-mail or direct message communications regarding updates or products by following the unsubscribe instructions in the body of any message.

  * 

### Email Communications

We may contact you by e-mail or other equivalent electronic communications if you access NinjaCat products or services. By registering or using NinjaCat Services, you specifically consent to the receipt of these e-mail or text message communications. If you do not want to receive emails or other communications from us, please follow the unsubscribe instructions in the body of such communications or notify us by email at support@NinjaCat.io.

## How We Protect Your Personal Information

NinjaCat has implemented reasonable security mechanisms to protect NinjaCat Client Information and Client’s User Data that is maintained on NinjaCat’ servers from loss, misuse and unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration and destruction. Examples of these security mechanisms include limited and password-protected access, high security public/private keys, encryption on processed data, and SSL encryption to protect transmission of data. 

However, please keep in mind that no security system is impenetrable. It may be possible for third parties to intercept or access NinjaCat Client Information and Client’s User Data in spite of these measures. NinjaCat cannot guarantee the security of your information and cannot be held responsible for unauthorized access to NinjaCat client accounts.

## Our Policy Toward Children

Our Site and Service is not directed to children under 13. We do not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under 13 or from websites that are targeted to children under 13. If you are under 13, please do not attempt to register or send any information about yourself to us, including your name, address, telephone number, or email address. If a parent or guardian becomes aware that his or her child has provided us with personally identifiable information without their consent, he or she should contact us at support@NinjaCat.io. If we become aware that a child under 13 has provided us with personally identifiable information, we will delete such information from our servers.

## Changes to this Privacy Policy

NinjaCat retains the discretion to amend or modify this Privacy Policy from time to time. If we make material changes to the way we collect, use or disclose Personally Identifying Information, we will notify you by posting a clear and prominent announcement on NinjaCat or through a direct communication to your NinjaCat account. 

Use and disclosure of information we obtain is subject to the later of: (1) the Privacy Policy in effect at the time such information is collected or (2) any subsequent Privacy Policy of which you have constructive notice. Your continued access to or use of NinjaCat following constructive notice of material changes to this Privacy Policy shall constitute consent to any amendments and/or modifications.

## How to Contact Us

NinjaCat welcomes any questions or comments about this Privacy Policy or our privacy practices. Any such comments or questions should be submitted via e-mail to: support@NinjaCat.io.

## How to Contact Us

This Privacy Policy is effective as of January 01, 2013.
